

Applicant for:

## [Remote] Senior Software Developer (.NET, ReactJS)

Futurify 29 March 2024

## thuanphamn.it

★ thuanphamn.it@gmail.com

Main interests: .NET, C#

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Dear HR,

This letter expresses my interest in your posting for a senior backend developer. With hands-on experience using .Net languages for years, I am confident I will match closely with your listed requirements. I've also attached my CV which details my experience.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to speaking with you about this opportunity.

Sincerely,

Thuan Pham

<sup>&</sup>quot;Hiring the wrong person is the most costly mistake you can make." - Brian Tracy







# PHAM NGOC THUAN

### .NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### Contact

0979130487

thuanphamn.it@gmail.com

#### Education

University of Science, HCM Bachelor of Information Technology Colleges

#### **Key Skills**

- ✓ Experience in C#, ASP.NET, MVC.NET, ADO.NET, HTML, CSS, JavaScript (jQuery).
- ✓ Experience in ORM (Entity Framework), MS SQL Server (T-SQL/Store Procedures)
- ✓ Experience in SVN/Git source control, JIRA.
- ✓ Experience in Object Oriented Programming, DI/IoC, and SOLID Principles.
- ✓ Fundamental knowledge: Go, CI/CD with Jenkins and GitHub action, Cloud with AWS, Docker, Postgres.

#### **Summary**

I'm a hardworking, dedicated, and responsible person. I can work independently or in a group with minimal supervision and can take the pressure to deliver quality work. With more than 8 years of experience performing, I can approach workflow quickly and complete all the tasks on time.

#### **Experience**

02.2020 - Present

Senior Software Engineer • NVG Technology, HCMC

Autoscout24/MotoScout24 project is an online marketplace platform for new/used vehicles in Switzerland. It supports sellers manage their businesses and approaching many customers by making the search for the dream vehicle and experience for users.

#### \* Responsibilities:

- Migrate the legacy project to the .Net Core.
- Maintain the existing features.
- Implement and perform unit tests for the new features.
- Investigate and fix bugs.

#### **❖** Technologies:

- C# (both .Net Framework and .Net core), T-SQL/Store Procedures (MS SQL Server), Golang.
- Web MVC.Net, Web API, Entity Framework, Docker, AWS.

03.2019 - 01.2020.

Senior Software Engineer • KPMG Vietnam, HCMC

The procurement system project of the sports equipment is to provide a solution that the procurement request application could be directly submitted to the person who is able to approve that request or not. How? the system will detect the kinds of requests and assign them to the approver and remind that person if the request is not taken yet later.

#### \* Responsibilities:

- Implement and perform unit tests for the features. o Investigate and fix the existing bugs.
- Assign and review the implement of team members.

#### \* Technologies:

- The Intelledox platform.
- C#, T-SQL/Store Procedures (MS SQL Server).

Senior Software Engineer • NashTech Vietnam, HCMC

The Contract System project is to manage all the stuff related to the contracts of the NashTech employees in the Europe location such as contracts, time working logs, salary, and other benefits, ... The SMI Index project is to display the statistics data in complex charts that would help the viewers has a looking visualization more.

#### \* Responsibilities:

- Maintain the existing features.
- Implement and perform unit tests for the new features.
- Investigate and fix bugs.

#### \* Technologies:

- C#, T-SQL/Store Procedures (MS SQL Server), JavaScript.
- Web MVC.Net, Web API, Entity Framework, jQuery, d3j.

11.2016 - 09.2017

Senior Software Engineer • Thien Minh Hoa Binh, HCMC

The BRS project is a Buffalo Tours Reservation System to manage all the information such as tour, tour guide, passenger, hotel, and booking. Besides that, it calculates the price of the tour/service to provide a good proposal. It also has APIs that provides the partner to consume our data and to connect with the system of partner/client like Flight Center, Expedia, and Viator, ...

#### \* Responsibilities:

- Maintain the existing features.
- Implement and perform unit tests for the new features.
- Investigate and fix bugs.

#### **❖** Technologies:

- C#, T-SQL/Store Procedures (MS SQL Server), JavaScript.
- Web MVC.Net, WCF, Window Form, ADO.Net, Entity Framework, jQuery.

05.2013 - 10.2016

Senior Software Engineer • The Promotion Factory Vietnam, HCMC

The Job Costing project is a part of the financial system that collects all data from other systems such as order, procurement, supplier, and data warehouse, which helps the finance guys visualize how the cost is.

#### \* Responsibilities:

- Work closely with the financial guys to collect the requirement.
- Implement and perform unit tests for the features.
- Provide the financial reports.
- Maintain and implement features of other systems.

#### ❖ Technologies:

- C#, T-SQL/Store Procedures (MS SQL Server), JavaScript.
- Web MVC.Net, ADO.Net, Entity Framework, jQuery, KendoUI.

03.2012 - 04.2013

Software Engineer • Mat Bao Network, HCMC

The reseller project is to manage the information on hosting, domain names, and so on... that the reseller could sell them by himself on this system.

#### \* Responsibilities:

- Maintain the existing features.
- Implement and perform unit tests for the features.
- Maintain and implement features of other systems.
- Investigate and fix bugs.

#### \* Technologies:

- C#, T-SQL/Store Procedures (MS SQL Server), JavaScript.
- Web form ASP.Net, ADO.Net, jQuery.

#### References

Please do not hesitate to contact me if you require references from any of my previous employers.